

### ♣ Profile

FullStack developer specialized in web and movil technologies, with a lot of passion creating with quality and good code the projects, using Angular & React for front-end and Ionic & React Native for mobile. I also worked with back-end creating APIS in NodeJS, Express & NESTJS. With a solid track record in the industry, I have held roles in both. Front-end and Back-end development in various companies. In the last year, I had the privilege of being part of the founding team of a startup, contributing significantly to the acquisition of its first software projects (UDigitalBusiness). Additionally, worked on AWS services.

# Employment History

### Fullstack Web Developer at YoContigolt, Guadalajara

June 2023 — Present

- Actively managed and coded for multiple projects, balancing project leadership with hands-on programming. Demonstrated adaptability and technical proficiency in both managerial and development.
- Spearheaded the development and ongoing maintenance of responsive web and mobile applications. Utilized a robust tech stack including NestJS, Angular, Node.js, and Ionic,
- Designed and implemented Docker architecture for projects, enhancing deployment efficiency and scalability.
- I specialize in developing high-performance mobile apps for festivals and large events using the Ionic framework with Angular.
- AWS managed and optimized services, including EC2 instances, Lambda functions, RDS databases, IAM Security policies and S3 buckets. Developed and deployed scalable secure to ensure high availability cloud infrastructure security.

### Fullstack Web Developer at Grupo Staff, Guadalajara

March 2022 — June 2023

- Implemented web solutions for SAT 4.0 billing, with Angular for frontend interactions, NodeJS for backend services and C# for business logic and system integrations.
- Using Azure DevOps for end-to-end software lifecycle management, including agile planning, version control with Git and deploying Node.js projects to Azure Cloud Services.
- Creating mobile applications using the latest in technology frameworks, Ionic and React. Our mastery of Ionic enables us to deliver versatile hybrid apps that seamlessly blend the best of web and native functionalities, offering a consistent user experience across both Android and iOS platforms and the projects are for México Billing & schools.

#### **Details**

Guadalajara Mexico 33 2034 7075 antach.vihe@gmail.com

### Links

github profile UDigital Business

#### Skills

JavaScript

**TypeScript** 

HTML & CSS

Git

Github

Angular (Web Framework)

React

Node.js

AWS

Ionic

Nest

**Express** 

MySQL

MongoDB

Web Applications

Version Control

Management

Docker (Software)

Agile Software Development

Software Lifecycle

Management

Azure DevOps

**Azure Cloud Services** 

DevOps

## Founder at UDigital Business, Guadalajara, Jal.

January 2024 — Present

As the founder of a thriving software development company, I have successfully spearheaded the delivery of multiple innovative projects that have significantly impacted various industries. With a hands-on approach to every facet of the business, I have played a pivotal role in all phases of development—from ideation and coding to deployment. Beyond the technical aspects, my role is multifaceted, encompassing critical business functions such as marketing and sales.

# Education

Software Developer, CETI, Centro de Enseñanza Técnica

January 2018 — January 2022

Computer Engineering, CUCEI, UDG. Online

January 2023 — Present

C1, Proulex English

January 2020 — December 2020

English School

### Languages

English

Spanish